Guide to the Cornell Society of Hotelmen records, 1928-1997.
Cornell Society of Hotelmen records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell Society of Hotelmen records, 1928-1997.
28-5-1797
Cornell Society of Hotelmen.
3.3 cubic ft.
Correspondence, reports, financial records.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes bulletins, correspondence, reports, receipts, minutes, bylaws, membership lists, treasurer's reports, class rosters, and other records of the Cornell Society of Hotelmen pertaining to hotel legislation, Cornell University School of Hotel Administration, Society events, and other related topics.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes bulletins, correspondence, reports, receipts, minutes, bylaws, membership lists, treasurer's reports, class rosters, and other records of the Cornell Society of Hotelmen pertaining to hotel legislation, Cornell University School of Hotel Administration, Society events, and other related topics.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell Society of Hotelmen.; Cornell University. School of Hotel Administration -- Societies, etc.
Subjects:
Hotel management.; Hotelkeepers.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
See also School of Hotel Administration Photographs and Ephemera, #28-10-4164 for photographs of Hotelmen luncheons (1929, 1930, 1950)
CONTAINER LIST
- Address List, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Form sent to Alumni for information, no date (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Proposals for Associate Membership, 1942-1953 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Form to alumni from Auditing Committee, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Proposed Amendment to By-Laws, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Candidates for President, 1928-1934 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Bulletin Committee Report, 1948, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Correspondence Concerning By-laws, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Officers by Years, 1928-1977 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- By-laws, 1929-1954 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Lists of those who received Membership Cards, 1936-1944 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Ledgers, 1948-1960 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Ledgers, 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Ledgers, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Children's Benefit Program, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Lists of Members, 1942-1948 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Correspondence, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Correspondence, 1941-1942 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Lists of Members, 1925-1950 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Correspondence, forms, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Memos sent to Alumni and Correspondence, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Correspondence, Board of Directors List, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Lists of Cornell Hotelmen in the Armed Forces, 1940-1949 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Minutes of Meetings of the Cornell Charter of Hotel Greeters of America, 1947-1949 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Correspondence, 1945-1950 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Correspondence, 1932-1934 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Correspondence, 1929-1936 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Report of the Committee to Determine how Alumni can assist Undergraduates, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Correspondence - Alphabetical Order, 1937-1946 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Correspondence concerning Loans, 1938-1944 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Correspondence-alphabetical order, 1942-1946 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Correspondence about Loan Fund, 1951-1955 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Correspondence concerning Meek Fund, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Status of Classes with Respect to Payment of Dues, 1933-1937 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Minutes of Meetings and By-laws, 1929-1930 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Correspondence with Martha Van Rensselaer, 1929-1931 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Meetings of Board of Director's Meetings, 1931-1932 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Meetings of Board of Director's Meetings, 1935-1956 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Treasurer's Reports, 1935-1972 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Minutes of Meetings, Reports, Correspondence, 1929-1934 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Minutes of Meetings, Reports, Correspondence, 1934-1935 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Minutes of Meetings, Reports, Correspondence, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Minutes of Meetings, Reports, Correspondence, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, Programs, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Minutes of Meetings, Correspondence, By-laws, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Minutes of Meetings, Reports, Correspondence, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Minutes of Meetings, Reports, Correspondence, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Minutes of Meetings, Reports, Correspondence, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Minutes of Meetings, Reports, Correspondence, 1939-1941 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Minutes of Meetings, Reports, Correspondence, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Minutes of Meetings, Reports, Correspondence, 1934-1942 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Minutes of Meetings, Reports, Correspondence, 1942-1944 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Minutes of Meetings, Reports, Correspondence, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Minutes of Meetings, Reports, Correspondence, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Minutes of Meetings, Reports, Correspondence, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Minutes of Meetings, Reports, Correspondence, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Minutes of Meetings, Reports, Correspondence, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Minutes of Meetings, Reports, Correspondence, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Minutes of Meetings, Reports, Correspondence, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Minutes of Meetings, Reports, Correspondence, By-laws, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Minutes of Meetings, Reports, Correspondence, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Minutes of Meetings, Reports, Correspondence, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Minutes of Meetings, Reports, Correspondence, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Minutes of Meetings, Reports, Correspondence, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Minutes of Meetings, Reports, Correspondence, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 26-27)
- Minutes of Meetings, Reports, Correspondence, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 28-29)
- Minutes of Meetings, Reports, Correspondence, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 30-31)
- Minutes of Meetings, Reports, Correspondence, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Minutes of Meetings, Reports, Correspondence, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Minutes of Meetings, Reports, Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Minutes of Meetings, Reports, Correspondence, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Minutes of Meetings, Reports, Correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Minutes of Meetings, 1967-1970 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Budgets, 1967-1975 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Minutes of Meetings - Various Committees, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Minutes of Meetings - Various Committees, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Minutes of Meetings - Various Committees, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Minutes of Meetings - Various Committees, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Triad Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Triad Committee, 1985-1987 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Report on Examination of Financial Statements, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Correspondence - Robert Beck, 1955-1959 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Correspondence - John Courtney, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Correspondence, 1930-1931 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Correspondence includes lists of alumni in the Armed Services, 1940-1953 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Correspondence and Reports, 1950s (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Programs, Memos, Correspondence, 1927-1929 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Smoker Files - Committee Files, Correspondence, Programs, 1929-1949 (Box 2, Folder 43-46)
- Publication - Cornell Innkeeper, 1950-05;1953-04;1961-05;1965-11;1966-05 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Publication - Cornell Innkeeper, 1968-05;1989;1990 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  Includes Fall and Winter issues for 1989 and the Fall issue for 1990
- Thumbnail Sketch of the Origin of the Cornell Society of Hotelmen - by John Courtney, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Annual Reception Program, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- European Chapter Society of Hotelmen 30th Anniversary Book 1961-1991, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- European Chapter Society of Hotelmen 20th Anniversary Book 1961-1981, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Cornellian Council Bulletins (1936-1939)and various other publications, 1930-1949 (Box 3)
- Correspondence, 1930-1959 (Box 3)
- Directory of the Cornell Society of Hotelmen, 1925-1962 (Box 3)
- New York State Hotel Association Bulletins, 1940-1949 (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
- Class Lists, 1939-1952 (Box 4, Folder 3-6)
- Correspondence to and from Robert Trier and Publications, 1927-1942 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Hotelmen Meeting - Address Given by John Crandall, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Photographs used in Bulletins of the Cornell Society of Hotelmen (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Stationery, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Hotel School History - Correspondence, Memos about the Book Proposed, 1987-1989 (Box 4, Folder 23-24)
- John MacFarlane Howie - Correspondence, 1939-1945 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Leadership Files, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Leadership Files, 1993-1995 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Bullets from Bill Eaton, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Membership - Correspondence, Meeting Minutes, 1987-1989 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Membership - Correspondence, Meeting Minutes, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Membership - Correspondence, Meeting Minutes, 1991-1992-06 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Membership - Correspondence, Meeting Minutes, 1992-07-1994 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- John Roberts - Membership Correspondence, 1951-1975 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- John H. Sherry - Membership Correspondence, 1951-1969 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Ballots and Membership Cards, 1972-1981 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Chapter Presidents, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Reception Invitations, 1959-1985 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Guest Books, 1984-1988, 1994 (Box 5)
- Notebook containing Alumni Statistics, 1925-1988 (Box 5)
- Class of 1928 Reunion Scrapbooks (Box 5)
- Alumni Organizational Study for Society's Long-Range Plan, 1986-1988 (Box 5)
- Asia Pacific Regional Conference - Tokyo, 1997 (Box 5)